{
	"data": [
    {
      "question": "If you (not do) .......... anything really bad, your job here will be quite safe.",
      "a": "won't do",
      "b": "don't do",
      "c": "are not doing",
      "answer": "2",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "41",
      "subcategorylv2": "2",
      "type": "2"
    },
    {
      "question": "If you take my advice, you (not have) ........... problems any more.",
      "a": "won't have",
      "b": "don't have",
      "c": "aren't having",
      "answer": "1",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "41",
      "subcategorylv2": "2",
      "type": "2"
    },
    {
      "question": "I'm sure that if I talk to him sweetly enough he (hold) ......... on and not look elsewhere.",
      "a": "holds",
      "b": "will hold",
      "c": "is holding",
      "answer": "2",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "41",
      "subcategorylv2": "2",
      "type": "2"
    },
    {
      "question": "So if I don't hear from you, I (assume) ......... everything is fine.",
      "a": "will assume",
      "b": "assume",
      "c": "is assuming",
      "answer": "1",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "41",
      "subcategorylv2": "2",
      "type": "2"
    },
    {
      "question": "I'll only call you if I think there (be) ......... a problem.",
      "a": "will be",
      "b": "is",
      "c": "is being",
      "answer": "2",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "41",
      "subcategorylv2": "2",
      "type": "2"
    },
    {
      "question": "I (be) .......... very pleased if you make it.",
      "a": "will be",
      "b": "am",
      "c": "am being",
      "answer": "1",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "41",
      "subcategorylv2": "2",
      "type": "2"
    },
    {
      "question": "If the plan (succeed) ......... you will make a profit.",
      "a": "will succeed",
      "b": "succeeds",
      "c": "is succeeding",
      "answer": "2",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "41",
      "subcategorylv2": "2",
      "type": "2"
    },
    {
      "question": "If he (not get) ........... a big order he will go bankrupt.",
      "a": "won't get",
      "b": "doesn't get",
      "c": "isn't getting",
      "answer": "2",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "41",
      "subcategorylv2": "2",
      "type": "2"
    },
    {
      "question": "I (bring) .......... my laptop if we have to look at the documents.",
      "a": "bring",
      "b": "will bring",
      "c": "am bringing",
      "answer": "2",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "41",
      "subcategorylv2": "2",
      "type": "2"
    },
    {
      "question": "If I read this manual, I (not make) .......... any mistakes.",
      "a": "won't make",
      "b": "don't make",
      "c": "am not making",
      "answer": "1",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "41",
      "subcategorylv2": "2",
      "type": "2"
    }
  ]
}